## **JESUS LIANG**

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



## PERSONAL PROFILE

Hi! I'm a professional Javascript and Typescript fullstack developer with 2 years of experience in software development. I'm a quick learner and always interested to get more skills. I like to get the job done, coding and solving problems!

## **SKILLS**

PROFICIENT:

- -HTML5/CSS3
- -Javascript/ES6
- -Typescript
- -SASS/SCSS
- -SASS/SC:
- -Redux
- -NextJS -SQL/MYSQL
- -NOSQL/MongoDB
- -Node.js/Express
- -Git/Github/Gitlab
- -Webpack
- -Rest and GraphQL
- -Rest and -Nginx
- -CI/CD

## EXPOSURE:

- -PHP/Laravel
- -Angular
- -Apache
- -Java

### OTHER:

- -Intermediate English
- -Photoshop/Illustrator
- -AdobeXD/Figma
- -Analytical skills
- -Communication skills
- -Leadership

## **CONTACT INFORMATION**

- 633 667 772
- @ Jesusliang96@gmail.com
- Cádiz, ES
- jesusliang.com
- in linkedin.com/in/jesus-liang

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **React Developer**

CESA Management Solutions 2020/12 - 2021/05

Project: https://www.leaderslinked.com

Migrated a legacy Social Web application written in Jquery to React and used Webpack to bundle and compile the application to integrate it to an existing PHP backend service

#### **Frontend Lead**

Availroom SL 2021/06 - present

#### Projects:

Availroom OS:

https://www.availroom.com/productos/pms-vrms

Led a small team to create a PMS/Channel Manager SaaS product, a web application using React and Redux for state management and we used libraries like Reselect for advanced optimization of the project to display large amounts of data. Created a Nodejs microservice to provide real-time user interactions like figma and implemented CI/CD through github actions for automated project deployment.

• Embeddable Booking Engine:

https://www.availroom.com/productos/motor-de-reservas

Created a booking engine with React and we used Webpack for advanced bundling and compiled the application to be embeddable in clients websites, allowing them to use our product to offer their hotels and apartments to the public, we have implemented complex algorithms and data structures to allow multiple renting of a room in a period of time

Availroom Checkin:

https://www.availroom.com/productos/app-huesped-availguest

Developed an web application to allow the customer to "check-in" when renting rooms in a hotel. Implemented an SDK to extract data through photos of documentations such as ID cards, passports and driver's licenses and connected to domotic electronic doors to allow customers to enter their accommodation through the application.

## **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

# Electronic Engineering in Computation (2015 - 2018)

Yacambú University (Venezuela)

# HTML and CSS Advanced Course (2018)

Cadi F1 (Venezuela)

## Professional Master in Multi-platform Application Development (2019 - Present)

Master D - Escuela Profesional (Málaga)